A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, general correspondence, RG 2, 1952-1957 FA425
Rockefeller Archive Center
- General Correspondence, 1954
  - Sweden, 1954; 1954/800
    - Sweden - (A-Z), 1954 (Box 49, Folder 328)
    - Sweden - Medical Sciences, 1954; 1954/800.A
      - Sweden - (A-Z), 1954 (Box 49, Folder 329)
    - Sweden - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1954; 1954/800.E
      - Sweden - (A-Z), 1954 (Box 49, Folder 329)
  - Switzerland, 1954; 1954/803
    - Switzerland - (A-Z), 1954 (Box 49, Folder 329)
    - Switzerland - Medical Sciences, 1954; 1954/803.A
      - Switzerland - (A-Z), 1954 (Box 49, Folder 330)
    - Switzerland - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1954; 1954/803.E
      - Switzerland - (A-Z), 1954 (Box 49, Folder 330)
    - Switzerland - Health Services, 1954; 1954/803.K
      - Switzerland - (A-Z), 1954 (Box 49, Folder 330)
  - Near East Region, 1954; 1954/804
    - Near East Region, 1954 (Box 49, Folder 330)
    - Near East Region - Humanities and Arts, 1954; 1954/804.R
      - Near East Region, 1954 (Box 49, Folder 330)
  - Turkey, 1954; 1954/805
    - Turkey - (A-Z), 1954 (Box 49, Folder 331)
    - Turkey - Medical Sciences, 1954; 1954/805.A
      - Turkey, 1954 (Box 49, Folder 331)
    - Turkey - Nursing, 1954; 1954/805.C
      - Turkey, 1954 (Box 49, Folder 331)
    - Turkey - Natural Sciences, 1954; 1954/805.D
      - Turkey, 1954 (Box 49, Folder 331)
    - Turkey - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1954; 1954/805.E
      - Turkey, 1954 (Box 49, Folder 331)
  - Crete, 1954; 1954/807
    - Crete, 1954 (Box 50, Folder 332)
  - Jordan, 1954; 1954/816
    - Jordan, 1954 (Box 50, Folder 332)
    - Jordan - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1954; 1954/816.E
      - Jordan, 1954 (Box 50, Folder 332)
  - Israel, 1954; 1954/825
    - Israel, 1954 (Box 50, Folder 333)
    - Israel - (A-Z), 1954 (Box 50, Folder 334)
    - Israel - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1954; 1954/825.D
      - Israel - (A-Z), 1954 (Box 50, Folder 335)
    - Israel - Social Sciences, 1954; 1954/825.S
      - Israel - (A-Z), 1954 (Box 50, Folder 335)
  - Lebanon, 1954; 1954/833
    - Lebanon - (A-Z), 1954 (Box 50, Folder 336)
    - Lebanon - Nursing, 1954; 1954/833.C
      - Lebanon, 1954 (Box 50, Folder 337)
    - Lebanon - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1954; 1954/833.D
      - Lebanon, 1954 (Box 50, Folder 337)
    - Lebanon - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1954; 1954/833.E
      - Lebanon, 1954 (Box 50, Folder 337)
    - Lebanon - Humanities and Arts, 1954; 1954/833.R
      - Lebanon, 1954 (Box 50, Folder 337)
- General Correspondence, 1955
  - International, 1955; 1955/100
    - Academic Freedom - Aitken, Thomas H. G.-Publications - Anderson, C.R.-Publications, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Anderson, Richmond - Atomic Energy, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Baird, G. B. - Balfour, Marshall C.-Publications, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Barnard, C.I - Bauer, J.H. - Belknap, Chauncey - Bevier, George - Blanton, M. - Brackett, E., 1955 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Bradfield, Richard, Janurary-June 1955 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Bradfield, Richard, July-December 1955 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Buchanan, N. S., 1955 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Bugher, John C.-Publications, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Buller, R. E. - Burden, Robert P., 1955 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Carr, Henry - Carter, J.C. - Casals, J. - Pulbications - Causey, O. - Publications, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Chandler, Robert F., 1955 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - China Medical Board - Clarke, D. H. - Publications, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Classification of Knowledge, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Classification of Knowledge-Supplementary Information, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Classification of Knowledge-Supplementary Information, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Cobb, William C., 1955 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Congress for Cultural Freedom, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Council of Foreign Relations, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Council on Foreign Relations - (A-Z) - Council for International Organizations - Crowder, L. V., 1955 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - D'Arms, Edward F. - Debevoise, T. - DeVinney, L. C., 1955 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Diplomatic Service - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Diplomatic Service - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Downs, W. G. - Publications, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - ECAFE - Population Growth - ECE (Lary) - Econometric Society Education - English Speaking Union - Evans, R.F., 1955 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Fahs. Charles, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - (F), 1955 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Gibler, John W., 1955 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Gilette, H. M. - Gilpatric, Chadbourne, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Grant, John B. - Publications, 1955 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Gray, George W. - Gregg, A., 1955 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Halprin, James R., 1955 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Harrar, J. George, 1955 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Harrison, W. - Harwood, R. E. - Hayes, G. B., 1955 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Heidrick, L. - Hill, Rolla - Publications - Hirst, Esther Mary - Hoyt, W. A., 1955 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - (In-InterAmerican), 1955 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - International -1-, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - International -2-, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Janney, J.H., 1955 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Johnson, H. N. - Publications, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - Johnson, L.A. - (Junior), 1955 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - Kerr, J. A. - Publications, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - Kimball. Lindsley, F., 1955 (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - Knipe, F. W. - Publications - Kokernot, R. H., 1955 (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - Lambert, R. A. - (League) - Lee, Ivy - List Society - Literature - Logan, J. A., 1955 (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - Mc Coy, Oliver M., 1955 (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - McIntosh, W. A. - McKelvey, J. A., 1955 (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - Magoon, E. H. - Mahaffy, A. F., 1955 (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - Maier, John, 1955 (Box 7, Folder 48)
    - Mailing Lists, 1955 (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - Marshall, John, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 50)
    - Melnick, Joseph - Milan, D. F. - Miller, Harry M., 1955 (Box 8, Folder 51)
    - Morrison, Robert S. - (Mo-O), 1955 (Box 8, Folder 52)
    - Paine, J. M. - Parker, Dorothy - Paul, J. H. - Payne, George - Peterson, O. L., 1955 (Box 8, Folder 53)
    - Pino, John A. - Poliomylitis - Pomerat, G. R. - Population, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 54)
    - Rachie, M.S. - Research Aid Funds, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 55)
    - Rhind, F. M., 1955 (Box 8, Folder 56)
    - Roberts, L. M., 1955 (Box 9, Folder 57)
    - Ruppert, J. A. - Ruppel, R. F., 1955 (Box 9, Folder 58)
    - Rusk, Dean, 1955 (Box 9, Folder 59)
    - Russell, Paul F. - Publications, 1955 (Box 9, Folder 60)
    - Russell, Paul F. - Publications, 1955 (Box 9, Folder 61)
    - (Sasse, Bruce E. - Smith), 1955 (Box 9, Folder 62)
    - Smithburn, K. C. - Publications - South Pacific Commission - Sprague, F. W., 1955 (Box 9, Folder 63)
    - Stakman, F. C. - Stewart, J. B., 1955 (Box 10, Folder 64)
    - Struthers, R. R., 1955 (Box 10, Folder 65)
    - Taylor, Richard M. - Publications, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 66)
    - Tennant, M. E. - Theifer, Max - Publications - Thomas, L. A., 1955 (Box 10, Folder 67)
    - Thompson, K. W., 1955 (Box 10, Folder 68)
    - United Nations - (A-Ec), 1955 (Box 10, Folder 69)
    - UNESCO - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 10, Folder 70)
    - UNESCO - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 10, Folder 71)
    - United Nations - (F-Fao), 1955 (Box 11, Folder 72)
    - United Nations - (Fao/Blume-Z), 1955 (Box 11, Folder 73)
    - United Nations - WHO - (Universal), 1955 (Box 11, Folder 74)
    - United Nations - VanDyke, G. E. - Vincent, G. E. - Warrent, Andrew T., 1955 (Box 11, Folder 75)
    - Watson, Robert, Jan-Dec 1955 (Box 11, Folder 76)
    - Watson, Robert, Jan-Dec 1955 (Box 11, Folder 77)
    - Weaver, Warren, 1955 (Box 11, Folder 78)
    - Webb, Vanderbilt - Weir, John, 1955 (Box 12, Folder 79)
    - Welhausen, E. J. - Wernimont, Dale - Whitman - Willits, Joseph, 1955 (Box 12, Folder 80)
    - Work, Telford H., 1955 (Box 12, Folder 81)
    - (World-Young), 1955 (Box 12, Folder 82)
    - Congress for Cultural Freedom, 1955 (Box 65, Folder 406)
    - International Cancer Research Congress, 1955 (Box 65, Folder 407)
    - Rusk, Dean, 1955 (Box 65, Folder 408)
    - South Pacific Commission, 1955 (Box 65, Folder 409)
    - United Nations - Brohi, A. K., 1955 (Box 65, Folder 410)
    - International - Medical Sciences, 1955; 1955/100.A
      - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 12, Folder 83)
    - International - Nursing, 1955; 1955/100.C
      - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 12, Folder 83)
    - International - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1955; 1955/100.E
      - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 12, Folder 83)
    - International - Malaria, 1955; 1955/100.I
      - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 12, Folder 83)
    - International - Yellow Fever, 1955; 1955/100.O
      - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 12, Folder 83)
    - International - Social Sciences, 1955; 1955/100.S
      - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 12, Folder 83)
  - United States, 1955; 1955/200
    - United States - (Aa-Ama), 1955 (Box 12, Folder 84)
    - United States - American - (A-Com), 1955 (Box 13, Folder 85)
    - United States - American Council on Education, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 86)
    - United States - American Council on Education - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 13, Folder 87)
    - United States - (American D-F), 1955 (Box 13, Folder 88)
    - United States - (American Foundation for Political Education - AFSC), 1955 (Box 13, Folder 89)
    - United States - American - (G-K), 1955 (Box 13, Folder 90)
    - United States - American - (L-Phy), 1955 (Box 14, Folder 91)
    - United States - American Political Science Association, 1955 (Box 14, Folder 92)
    - United States - American Political Science Association - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 14, Folder 93)
    - United States - American - (Press-U), 1955 (Box 14, Folder 94)
    - United States - (An-Ar), 1955 (Box 14, Folder 95)
    - United States - (As-Associations for American), 1955 (Box 14, Folder 96)
    - United States - (Association for the Aid-Asociation Films), 1955 (Box 15, Folder 97)
    - United States - Association of Teachers of Preventative Medicine, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 98)
    - United States - (Association of Technical - At), 1955 (Box 15, Folder 99)
    - United States - (Ba-Be), 1955 (Box 15, Folder 100)
    - United States - (Bi), 1955 (Box 15, Folder 101)
    - United States - (Bl-Bron), 1955 (Box 15, Folder 102)
    - United States - (Broo), 1955 (Box 15, Folder 103)
    - United States - (Brow-Bu), 1955 (Box 16, Folder 104)
    - United States - (Ca-Carl), 1955 (Box 16, Folder 105)
    - United States - (Carnegie), 1955 (Box 16, Folder 106)
    - United States - (Carver-Cl), 1955 (Box 16, Folder 107)
    - United States - (Coe-College/A), 1955 (Box 16, Folder 108)
    - United States - (College/B-Colton, K.), 1955 (Box 16, Folder 109)
    - United States - Columbia University - (A-B), 1955 (Box 16, Folder 110)
    - United States - Columbia University - (C-K), 1955 (Box 17, Folder 111)
    - United States - Columbia University - (M-Z), 1955 (Box 17, Folder 112)
    - United States - (Com), 1955 (Box 17, Folder 113)
    - United States - (Con-Cornell), 1955 (Box 17, Folder 114)
    - United States - Cornell Medical School - (A-Z) - Cornell University, 1955 (Box 17, Folder 115)
    - United States - Cornell University - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 17, Folder 116)
    - United States - (Coro-Cu), 1955 (Box 17, Folder 117)
    - United States - (Da), 1955 (Box 18, Folder 118)
    - United States - (De-Dos), 1955 (Box 18, Folder 119)
    - United States - (Dou-Dw), 1955 (Box 18, Folder 120)
    - United States - (Ea-El), 1955 (Box 18, Folder 121)
    - United States - (Em-Ez), 1955 (Box 18, Folder 122)
    - United States - (Fa-Fei), 1955 (Box 18, Folder 123)
    - United States - Fels Research Institute, 1955 (Box 18, Folder 124)
    - United States - (Fi-Ford, G. B.), 1955 (Box 19, Folder 125)
    - United States - Ford Foundation - Appendices, 1955 (Box 19, Folder 0125A)
    - United States - Ford Foundation - New Yorker Profile, Nov 26; Dec 3, 10, 17; 1955 (Box 19, Folder 0125B)
    - United States - Ford Foundation - (A-Be), 1955 (Box 19, Folder 126)
    - United States - Ford Foundation - Behavioral Sciences - "Report on European Trip( Mental Health) Summer 1955" - Bernard Berelson (Box 19, Folder 0126A)
    - United States - Ford Foundation - (Br-H), 1955 (Box 19, Folder 127)
    - United States - Ford Foundation - India Program, 1955 (Box 19, Folder 128)
    - United States - Ford Foundation - (Indo-Z), 1955 (Box 20, Folder 129)
    - United States - (Fo-Fos), 1955 (Box 20, Folder 130)
    - United States - (Fou-Fr), 1955 (Box 20, Folder 131)
    - United States - Fulbright Program (A-Z) - Fund (A), 1955 (Box 20, Folder 132)
    - United States - Fund for Peaceful Atomic Development, Inc., 1955 (Box 20, Folder 133)
    - United States - Fund for Peaceful Atomic Development, Inc. - Application to Rockefeller Brothers Fund, March 14, 1955 (Box 20, Folder 134)
    - United States - Fund - (R-Z) - Fuselle, E., 1955 (Box 21, Folder 135)
    - United States - (Ga-Go), 1955 (Box 21, Folder 136)
    - United States - (Gr-Gu), 1955 (Box 21, Folder 137)
    - United States - (Ha-Hartford), 1955 (Box 21, Folder 138)
    - United States - Harvard University - (A-Law School), 1955 (Box 21, Folder 139)
    - United States - Harvard University - (A-Law School), 1955 (Box 21, Folder 140)
    - United States - Harvard University - (A-Law School), 1955 (Box 21, Folder 141)
    - United States - Harvard University - (Le-Z), 1955 (Box 22, Folder 142)
    - United States - Harvard University - (Le-Z), 1955 (Box 22, Folder 143)
    - United States - Harvard University - (Le-Z), 1955 (Box 22, Folder 144)
    - United States - (Harvard-Yenching-He), 1955 (Box 22, Folder 145)
    - United States - (Hi-Ho), 1955 (Box 22, Folder 146)
    - United States - (Hu-Hz), 1955 (Box 22, Folder 147)
    - United States - (Il-Insect), 1955 (Box 23, Folder 148)
    - United States - Institute - (A-Z) - InterAmerican, 1955 (Box 23, Folder 149)
    - United States - International - (A-Z) - (Inter University-Iverson), 1955 (Box 23, Folder 150)
    - United States - (Ja-John), 1955 (Box 23, Folder 151)
    - United States - Johns Hopkins University - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 23, Folder 152)
    - United States - (Johnson-Ju), 1955 (Box 23, Folder 153)
    - United States - (Ka-Ke), 1955 (Box 24, Folder 154)
    - United States - (Ki-Kz), 1955 (Box 24, Folder 155)
    - United States - (La-Lz), 1955 (Box 24, Folder 156)
    - United States - (La-Lz), 1955 (Box 24, Folder 157)
    - United States - (La-Lz), 1955 (Box 24, Folder 158)
    - United States - (Ma), 1955 (Box 24, Folder 159)
    - United States - (Me), 1955 (Box 25, Folder 160)
    - United States - (Mi-Midd), 1955 (Box 25, Folder 161)
    - United States - (Mik-Mon), 1955 (Box 25, Folder 162)
    - United States - (Mor-Nad), 1955 (Box 25, Folder 163)
    - United States - National - (A-Bi), 1955 (Box 25, Folder 164)
    - United States - National Book Committee - National Bureau of Statistics, 1955 (Box 25, Folder 165)
    - United States - National - (Ca-Com), 1955 (Box 26, Folder 166)
    - United States - National - (Con-Cz), 1955 (Box 26, Folder 167)
    - United States - National - (E-Institute of Arts and Letters), 1955 (Box 26, Folder 168)
    - United States - National - (Institute of Health-P), 1955 (Box 26, Folder 169)
    - United States - National - (R), 1955 (Box 26, Folder 170)
    - United States - National - (S-T), 1955 (Box 26, Folder 171)
    - United States - (Nav-New School), 1955 (Box 26, Folder 172)
    - United States - New York - (A-F), 1955 (Box 27, Folder 173)
    - United States - New York - (H-Z), 1955 (Box 27, Folder 174)
    - United States - (Newberry-No), 1955 (Box 27, Folder 175)
    - United States - (Nu-Oak), 1955 (Box 27, Folder 176)
    - United States - (Ob-Or), 1955 (Box 27, Folder 177)
    - United States - (Pa-Pan), 1955 (Box 27, Folder 178)
    - United States - Pan American Sanitary Bureau - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 28, Folder 179)
    - United States - Pan American Union - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 28, Folder 180)
    - United States - (Pap-Pe), 1955 (Box 28, Folder 181)
    - United States - (Ph-Pi), 1955 (Box 28, Folder 182)
    - United States - (Pl-Pr), 1955 (Box 28, Folder 183)
    - United States - Princeton University - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 29, Folder 184)
    - United States - (Pri-Pz), 1955 (Box 29, Folder 185)
    - United States - (Q-Reed), 1955 (Box 29, Folder 186)
    - United States - (Rei-Rob), 1955 (Box 29, Folder 187)
    - United States - Rockefeller - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 29, Folder 188)
    - United States - (Rockford-Rz), 1955 (Box 29, Folder 189)
    - United States - (Sa-Sap), 1955 (Box 30, Folder 190)
    - United States - (Sar-Sc), 1955 (Box 30, Folder 191)
    - United States - (Se-Sin), 1955 (Box 30, Folder 192)
    - United States - (Sio-Sl), 1955 (Box 30, Folder 193)
    - United States - (Sm-So), 1955 (Box 30, Folder 194)
    - United States - Social Science Research Council - Preventative Medicine, 1955 (Box 30, Folder 195)
    - United States - (Society-Southern), 1955 (Box 31, Folder 196)
    - United States - (Southwestern-Standard), 1955 (Box 31, Folder 197)
    - United States - Stanford - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 31, Folder 198)
    - United States - (Star-Str), 1955 (Box 31, Folder 199)
    - United States - (Stu-Sz), 1955 (Box 31, Folder 200)
    - United States - (Ta-Thomson), 1955 (Box 31, Folder 201)
    - United States - (Ti-Tz), 1955 (Box 32, Folder 202)
    - United States - (Union-United), 1955 (Box 32, Folder 203)
    - United States - United States Agriculture - (A-Ha), 1955 (Box 32, Folder 204)
    - United States - United States Agriculture - (He-Z), 1955 (Box 32, Folder 205)
    - United States - United States - (Ai-E), 1955 (Box 32, Folder 206)
    - United States - United States - F.O.A. - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 32, Folder 207)
    - United States - United States - (H-Im), 1955 (Box 33, Folder 208)
    - United States - United States Information Agency - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 33, Folder 209)
    - United States - United States Information Agency - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 33, Folder 210)
    - United States - United States - International Cooperation Administration, 1955 (Box 33, Folder 211)
    - United States - United States - I. C. A. - "Report on Community Development in Jamaica, Puerto Rico, Bolivia and Peru" - Verna A. Carley, Elmer A. Starch, Nov 1, 1955 (Box 33, Folder 212)
    - United States - United States - I. C. A. - "Report on Community Development in India, Pakistan and the Philippines" - Harold S. Adams, George M. Foster, Paul S. Taylor, Oct 5, 1955 (Box 33, Folder 213)
    - United States - United States - I. C. A. - (C-Z), 1955 (Box 33, Folder 214)
    - United States - United States - (S-Se), 1955 (Box 33, Folder 215)
    - United States - United States Public Health Service - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 34, Folder 216)
    - United States - United States - State - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 34, Folder 217)
    - United States - United States - State - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 34, Folder 218)
    - United States - United States - Supreme Court - University - (A-B), 1955 (Box 34, Folder 219)
    - United States - University of California - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 34, Folder 220)
    - United States - University of California - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 34, Folder 221)
    - United States - University of California - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 34, Folder 222)
    - United States - University of Chicago - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 35, Folder 223)
    - United States - University of Chicago - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 35, Folder 224)
    - United States - University of Chicago - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 35, Folder 225)
    - United States - University - (Cincinnati-G), 1955 (Box 35, Folder 226)
    - United States - University - (I-Miami), 1955 (Box 35, Folder 227)
    - United States - University of Michigan - (A-L), 1955 (Box 35, Folder 228)
    - United States - University of Michigan - (M-Z), 1955 (Box 36, Folder 229)
    - United States - University - (Micr-Minnesota/Grout), 1955 (Box 36, Folder 230)
    - United States - University - (Minnsota/Harris-Missouri), 1955 (Box 36, Folder 231)
    - United States - University - (N-O), 1955 (Box 36, Folder 232)
    - United States - University of Pennsylvania - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 36, Folder 233)
    - United States - University of Pittsburgh - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 36, Folder 234)
    - United States - University of Rhode Island - University of Rochester - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 37, Folder 235)
    - United States - University - (S-V), 1955 (Box 37, Folder 236)
    - United States - (University of Washington-V), 1955 (Box 37, Folder 237)
    - United States - University of Wisconsin - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 37, Folder 238)
    - United States - (Wa-Westchester), 1955 (Box 37, Folder 239)
    - United States - (Western-White), 1955 (Box 37, Folder 240)
    - United States - (Whittier-Williams), 1955 (Box 38, Folder 241)
    - United States - (Williamsburg-Woh), 1955 (Box 38, Folder 242)
    - United States - (Woodman-Wz), 1955 (Box 38, Folder 243)
    - United States - Yahkub, T. - Yale University - (A-Me), 1955 (Box 38, Folder 244)
    - United States - Yale University - (Mu-Z), 1955 (Box 38, Folder 245)
    - United States - (Ye-Z), 1955 (Box 38, Folder 246)
    - United States - Conservation Foundation - duPont - Far Eastern Association, 1955 (Box 65, Folder 411)
    - United States - Individual Capitalism - Maris, P. - NAACPstern Association, 1955 (Box 65, Folder 412)
    - United States - Sioux City, 1955 (Box 65, Folder 413)
    - United States - Thompson, F. - University of Vermont - Austin Institute, 1955 (Box 65, Folder 414)
    - United States - Medical Sciences, 1955; 1955/200.A
      - United States - (A-M), 1955 (Box 38, Folder 247)
      - United States - (N-T), 1955 (Box 39, Folder 248)
      - United States - University - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 39, Folder 249)
      - United States - University - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 39, Folder 250)
      - United States - (Up-Z), 1955 (Box 39, Folder 251)
      - University of California - Medical School, 1955 (Box 65, Folder 414)
    - United States - Nursing, 1955; 1955/200.C
      - United States - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 39, Folder 252)
    - United States - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1955; 1955/200.E
      - United States - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 39, Folder 253)
    - United States - Declinations, 1955; 1955/200.F
      - United States - (A-Z), 1955 (Box 39, Folder 253)
    - United States - Humanities and Arts, 1955; 1955/200.R
      - United States - (A-Ind), 1955 (Box 39, Folder 254)
      - United States - Institute of Contemporary Art - Industrial Design, 1955 (Box 40, Folder 255)
      - United States - Institute of Contemporary Art - Industrial Design, 1955 (Box 40, Folder 256)
      - United States - Institute of Contemporary Art - Industrial Design, 1955 (Box 40, Folder 257)
      - United States - (K-Z), 1955 (Box 40, Folder 258)
    - United States - Social Sciences, 1955; 1955/200.S
      - United States - (A-Columbia University/S), 1955 (Box 40, Folder 259)
      - United States - (Columbia University-Social Science) - (Cornell University-Social Sciences), 1955 (Box 40, Folder 260)
      - United States - Dartmouth College - Government - Foreign Service - Educational Foundation, 1955 (Box 41, Folder 261)
      - United States - Foreign Service - Educational Foundation - Social Science Research Council - (A-N), 1955 (Box 41, Folder 262)
      - United States - S. S. R. C. - Political Behavior, 1955 (Box 41, Folder 263)
      - United States - S. S. R. C. - Political Behavior, 1955 (Box 41, Folder 264)
      - United States - S. S. R. C. - (R-W) - (U-Z), 1955 (Box 41, Folder 265)
  - Alaska, 1955; 1955/202
    - Alaska, 1955 (Box 41, Folder 266)
  - California, 1955; 1955/205
    - California, 1955 (Box 41, Folder 266)
  - Panama Canal Zone, 1955; 1955/206
    - Canal Zone, 1955 (Box 41, Folder 266)
  - Guam, 1955; 1955/213